There are strange phenomenon
in this world
that science is unable to explain.
When people came
face to face with them,
all they can do is tremble
upon the terror of the darkness.
But there are those who fight every day
to shine a ray of hope
into that chaotic darkness.
People call them...
Psychics.
(MOB MOB WOW!)
I realized that our youth is Grey
The origin of this uneasiness
Is yet unknown
Trains of emotions keep running
Through my brain
Struggling through this adolescence
Don't disturb my deep psyche
Who is that behind you?
Opposing ideas creates distortion
Exorcise all the sorrow
So, do what you can now
My life
Finally, break it down
(Want) Both greed
(Young) And honesty
(Burn) Are growing
(1) On this chest of mine
(Trance) I'm not waking up
(Chance) I want to wake up
(Stance) These two different faces of mine
(1) Are standing back-to-back
Taking things as it is
In this free relation
where we resent each other
Once these two become one
That smile becomes one
And only "1"
(MOB MOB WOW!)
"1"
One and only "1"
(MOB MOB WOW!)
"1"
One and only "1"
Future aspirations form?
What, you haven't finished writing yours?
Yeah, I couldn't think of one...
I'm going to a university that
has a subject regarding UFOs.
I'll probably try
to get a work on a game company.
I just wrote office worker.
I'm still a first-year,
so I'm still thinking about it.
I see.
But all of you really
thought well about it.
By the way, apparently Takane
got accepted to Citrus Chilli High.
Citrus Chilli High? Isn't that...
Yeah, the one you need a deviation
score above 65 to enter.
One of the top three high-level
schools in the prefecture.
Well, she has a really good head
on her shoulders, unlike us.
Tsubomi is so amazing...
Wait, is that for real?
Citrus High has a joint business
with a high school in England,
so apparently you can get
to study abroad there.
Studying abroad sounds really nice.
(Progress until Mob explodes: 7%)
(Spirits and Such Consultation Office)
Right, I filled one of these
back at high school, too.
Well, good thing for you,
you already secured
your future workplace.
Huh?
This place, of course.
This job is your calling, isn't it?
Isn't this just a part-time job?
Now then, who knows?
In the future, there's a possibility
this will become a full-fledged
that hires multiple full-time
employees, you know?
Future, huh?
Have you already thought about making
a consultation office back in middle school?
What? Of course not.
What kind of middle schooler
would think of that?
So why did you end up doing it?
Huh?!
Why? Well, you see, one day...
I just realised that I have
a rare special ability.
It just also happens that I already
too good at my job at the time,
so I decided to challenge myself
with new things instead.
You did great at your job,
and then opened your own office.
You really are amazing, Master.
You could say that.
-I finished cleaning the toilet.
-Okay.
Hey, you don't have to report
every single thing you do, you know?
Y-yes, Sir.
Good day to you, Shigeo.
Uh, yeah...
We're going to have a client here soon.
Listen up, Serizawa!
You may already be formally hired here,
but you're still just a fresh newbie!
Make sure you watch closely how I handle
the customers and learn the basics.
Yes, Sir! I will do my best.
Serizawa is older than
Master Reigen, and yet...
I found this ornament at
an antique shop on my travel.
Now that I think about it, bad things
started happening ever since I got it.
I couldn't sleep properly.
People also said that
my complexion is looking worse.
Can you please see
if there's anything wrong with it?
Very well.
By the way, how much
did you buy it for?
I bought it for 80,000 yen.
So expensive.
So expensive...
As far as I checked,
I don't sense anything spiritual...
Master.
What is it, Mob?
I suggest you don't touch
that ornament any further.
Huh?
There's something like a grudge in it.
Tons of bad things are swirling in it.
I think it would be pretty dangerous
if we let it be.
On second thought,
we'll exorcise it.
Would you wait at the cafe
above this floor for a moment?
(Spirits and Such Consultation Office)
O-okay...
-Your opinion is duly noted, Mob.
-Yes?
So, Serizawa, what about you?
Me?
All I can see is that
it's a pretty wicked cursed ornament...
Look here, Serizawa.
Why are you just spacing around
without saying anything?
Let's say that if I "actually"
didn't realize it was cursed,
won't it be a big problem?
Huh? Uh...
All this was a test of whether
you'll notice my mistake or not.
Wha...?!
T-then, did I...?
Well, you're a newbie here,
so I'll go easy on you.
How about you try redeeming yourself?
-Try exorcising it on your own.
-Y-yes, Sir!
I did it.
How did it go, Mob?
Serizawa is really powerful.
All right!
Good job, Serizawa.
Keep up the good work.
That was from the impact just now...
I-it's my fault...!
I damaged this 80,000 yen ornament...!
I'll go get a loan!
Hold it!
Don't worry.
I'll do something about it.
W-what are you going to do...?
Rice Grain Big Bang!
A technique where Reigen unleashes
the maximum potential of a rice grain.
One of Reigen's many special technique.
I-it's fixed!
At this moment, Serizawa is impressed
by Reigen's limitless abilities
and learned for the first time
just how wide the world is.
What's wrong, Shige?
You're not moving your chopsticks.
I have to write down
my future aspirations,
but I have no idea what to write.
You still have like nearly 10 years
until you graduate from university,
so why not just write
office worker for now?
Come on, you're being too
simple-minded here.
I still haven't decided
which high school I'll attend either.
If you haven't found out
what you want to do,
then how about making a living
doing the things you're good at?
For you, it would be...
...a magician, perhaps?
-So simple-minded...
Come on, just write whatever,
it'll be okay.
Dimple.
Your future career won't be the same
as the one you wrote,
no matter what you do.
I can't do that,
this is related to my future.
You just can't ever lie, do you?
What about your future prospects, Dimple?
You're asking about
future prospects to a ghost?
You're just naturally brutal, you know?
Right.
Sorry...
Wait a sec...
Wasn't there something I wanted to do...?
That's right!
I forgot about it all this time!
(Body Improvement Club)
Future aspirations, huh?
My family runs a farm.
After I finish high school,
I might have to succeed them.
I'll just prioritize entering
high school for now.
I got a recommendation to be an athlete.
I'll look for a job
where I can train my muscles.
My parents wants me to be a civil servant,
but my grades aren't that good...
I like animals, so I decided that
I would be a veterinarian.
You said you want to be a manga artist,
didn't you, Onigawara?
Goddammit, Gouda!
How could you tell them?!
-You said that you want to study
-Hey! You don't have to say it out loud!
-to enter a co-ed high school with a manga club.
Everyone pretty much has decided
what they want in their future...
Well, I have an thinking
about it all this time,
but looking at your expression,
there's no more doubt.
Mezato. What are you talking about?
About the recent terrorist attack.
While the world only thinks of it as vandalism
in the middle of a natural disaster,
I'm sure that it's actually a fight
to decide the very fate of the world.
In that fight, you managed
to defeat the evil organization,
but you also lost something important.
Isn't that right?
No, I'm just thinking about
my future aspirations.
No way! Just look at that!
I'm totally sure that
you're related to that thing!
Some even started calling it
the Divine Tree.
People are starting to worship it.
You should come out and tell everyone
that you're the creator of the Divine Tree.
Is this related to that thing
you mentioned before?
The Psycho Helmet Cult!
Do you want to correlate
the two of them?
(Psycho Helmet Cult)
Exactly! You catch pretty quick for once!
You truly are amazing, Mob.
I can't believe someone as mystical
as you is actually my classmate.
Looking back at my entire life,
you might be the biggest thing
that ever happened.
Mezato, have you decided what
you'll become in the future?
Huh? What's with this
all of the sudden?
I'll probably be a cameraman.
That, or a journalist.
I'm sure you'll find a lot more
exciting things in your future.
Uh, I doubt there are many things
that can rival that.
I'm not talking about some grand speech
or something physically big.
Then, like what?
For me, it's like when I joined
the Body Improvement Club.
What's so big about that?
It's not that different
from what you said.
After all, that thing is just broccoli.
I see, it's just broccoli...
Yeah, right!
As if I'll agree to that!
Then what about you,
what will you do in the future?
The thing is, I couldn't think of any.
After all that talk, I'm glad
you still have zero persuasiveness.
Here I thought you got enlightened
or something after being too unpopular.
There's no mistaking it,
I'm possessed by an evil spirit.
I have contacted
many psychics before this,
but not a single one of them
can exorcise the evil spirit.
Uh... I see...
I myself believe
"They" are definitely here.
I knew it!
Hiring you was the right call!
"They" are so scary!
The cockroaches!
By the way, what are the exact specifics
that made you think that way?
For starters, my shoulders feel heavy,
and I've been having sleep paralysis.
There were also times when I developed
cavities even though I brushed my teeth.
Maybe I also got fired from my
part-time job thanks to that evil spirit.
A female co-worker kept saying that
I touched her butt even though I didn't.
I just grazed them with the back
of my hand. It's an accident, really.
Even my lover ran away
because of the evil spirit.
Oh, your lover...?
Yes. She was so young and nice.
When I told her I'm running out of money,
her attitude took a 180.
She's like an evil spirit herself.
She once said that I'm her type,
what a bunch of lies.
Oh, and I've been losing more
and more of my hair, too.
It's as if someone is ripping them away.
Is that so...
By the way, what's with
all the trash?
They're not trash!
They're my assets!
A barrier of sorts.
I can sleep soundly
if I'm surrounded by them.
A barrier?
What's this picture?
Roach!
An old picture of me,
back in my mischievous days.
-He never changed...
You two, listen to his story.
I'll go pick up a strong
exorcising tool...
Okay.
If nobody can exorcise my evil spirit,
then maybe my life
is pretty much finished.
Will I just keep on repeating
meaningless days until I die?
My parents died when I'm in my 20's,
my relatives cut all connections to me.
I don't have any connections,
so I can't get any jobs either.
Maybe my life actually
is already finished.
I know how you feel,
so very much.
When I was a shut-in, I always thought
that it might be how my life will end.
I'm also worried that I can't ever decide
on my future aspirations.
I've lived for 50 years.
A long, long 50 years,
yet the only thing I have left
is this house left by my parents.
I never obtained anything.
I just kept drifting around,
taking the easy choices.
If only I seriously thought about
which path to pick back then...
Your whole life can just end
the moment you make a single mistake...
Enough already,
that's too much of a bother.
There's no need to work so hard.
It's 490 yen for one.
It's 670 yen for two.
It's 540 yen for one.
Let's just do it tomorrow.
So tired, so lazy.
Let's just sleep for today.
Thankies.
Evil spirits absolutely hate clean room.
This should be...
W-what's going on?
Oh, you got to be kidding me!
That's from that trash house!
You too, no need to work so hard.
Are these the evil spirit's minions?!
No need to work that hard.
Let's just sleep already.
Double Hydrogenated Water Mist!
A technique where Reigen uses
dissolved hydrogen gas
to protect from evil spirit attacks.
One of his many special techniques.
Of the evil spirit, by the evil spirit,
for the evil spirit...
Hey, what the heck are you two doing?!
Oh, Master. You're back?
This isn't the time to say that!
Look, an evil spirit showed up!
Oh, you're right.
So he was possessed
by something so big.
No, I think that's actually
his vengeful spirit.
Whatever.
My power would be too strong and
may cause damage to the surroundings.
Do it, you two.
Of the evil spirit, by the evil spirit,
for the evil spirit...
Of the evil spirit...
Oh...
Was this room this spacious again?
Thank you so very much.
Thanks to you, I think I can think
positively about life from now on.
I'm glad to hear that, but...
Your roof got, uh, blown up, so...
My parents have it covered
with insurance, so it'll be okay.
Yes, you can always
rely on insurance.
Speaking of which,
think of this as insurance, too.
What's wrong, Serizawa?
Are you feeling sick?
I just can't ignore what he said...
I'm the same as him.
I lived for 30 years,
and I don't have anything.
You're not going to make it if you always
get affected by the customers.
Your life isn't over just yet.
If anything, you're lucky you noticed early
that you've done things you regretted.
Right, Mob?
I couldn't ignore what he said, either.
You too?!
I just haven't made any
huge mistakes yet,
but that day may actually come.
Just thinking about it makes me
too scared to pick any path.
You were thinking about
something like that?
Right, it's around the time
when he has to fill a future aspiration.
I think you will be all right, Serizawa.
You get to talk to many people
by working there,
and you get to learn from it.
But for me...
(Progress until Mob explodes: 18%)
So you're focusing on getting
to a high school for now, huh?
In the end, I still can't
come up with anything.
If you aim for a public school,
you have to improve your math
and geography grades.
You have to do better
on the next exams, Kageyama.
O-okay.
Is that it?
That said, having a clear goal
in the future
would help you plan your life better.
You don't have to hurry,
but it might be a problem
if you can't find one
before you become an adult.
Truth is, I only recently figured out that
I wanted to travel to many places alone.
Things would've gone much easier
had I thought of it when I was younger.
Then again, seeing how you did
on the marathon,
I think you'll be just all right.
Teacher...
Becoming a traveler actually
sounds pretty nice.
I'm actually quite worried about
how easily influenced you are...
(Spirits and Such Consultation Office)
I've been thinking about this
for quite a bit,
but I think my future career
won't be here in this office.
I see.
This place is comfortable,
and I can discuss anything with you.
But if I take that for granted...
I won't grow anything
other than my physical age.
I'm sorry, Master Reigen.
I can't fulfill my promise
to keep working here in the future.
Mob, that was obviously just a joke.
You will find many things
you want to do from now on.
You asked about why I opened
this consultation office, didn't you?
Oh, yes.
I gave you an answer back then,
but the truth is...
I got bored in the company I worked in,
and made this office on a whim.
Well, I got bored again in around a year
and was thinking of quitting.
It was exactly then when...
Well, this and that happened,
and it became what it is.
It might have started on a whim,
but it's not a lie that it has become
something I wanted to do.
Anyway, the things you want to do
doesn't have to be a job.
Just live the way you want it to be.
Master Reigen...
Got it!
Thank you very much.
Wait, we're still on working hours here...
(001: The Future ~Career Aspirations~)
Is he coming back?
Seems like the time has come.
The time for my era.
Those that squirm in the darkness
have started to make a move.
Can the cycle of sadness be severed?
Next on episode two of
Mob Psycho 100 III,
"Yokai Hunter Haruaki Amakusa appears!
~The Threat of Hundred Demons! ~"
Watching III in real-time
is also a wise decision.